<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Thorrwulf</title><link>https://lorenzozaccagnini.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Thorrwulf</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Lorenzo Zaccagnini- [Creative Commons Attribution 4.0 International License](https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by/4.0/).</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 00:03:47 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lorenzozaccagnini.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Intercept pending transactions with Rust</title><link>https://lorenzozaccagnini.github.io/posts/evm-intercept-tx-rad/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Nov 2022 00:03:47 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://lorenzozaccagnini.github.io/posts/evm-intercept-tx-rad/</guid><description>Transactions on blockchain are not instant. They are pending until they are confirmed by the network. This is a security feature of the blockchain. It is not possible to change the history of the blockchain. This is why it is important to wait for the transaction to be confirmed before sending another transaction. In this article we will see how to intercept pending transactions with rust.
1. Intercept pending transactions 1.</description></item><item><title>Develop an Ethereum bridge with Rust</title><link>https://lorenzozaccagnini.github.io/posts/evm-blockchain-rust-bridge/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 00:03:47 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://lorenzozaccagnini.github.io/posts/evm-blockchain-rust-bridge/</guid><description>A blockchain bridge is a system that allows the transfer of assets between two different blockchains. It is a crucial component of the blockchain ecosystem as it allows the interoperability of different blockchains. In this article, we will develop a bridge between two EVM-compatible blockchains. We will use the Rust programming language.
Rust is a programming language that is gaining popularity in the blockchain ecosystem. It is a multi-paradigm language that is safe, fast, and concurrent.</description></item><item><title>Develop an Ethereum oracle with Rust</title><link>https://lorenzozaccagnini.github.io/posts/simple-rust-oracle/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 00:03:47 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://lorenzozaccagnini.github.io/posts/simple-rust-oracle/</guid><description>A blockchain oracle is a service that allows smart contracts to interact with external data sources. In this post, we will develop a simple oracle that will track every time a Ethereum Name Service NFT is transferred. We will use Rust and the web3 crate to interact with the Ethereum blockchain.
Stay with me until the end to learn how to listen to events on the Ethereum blockchain, you will learn how events work and how to use them in your smart contracts and oracles.</description></item><item><title>Develop a Soulbound NFT using Foundry and Slither</title><link>https://lorenzozaccagnini.github.io/posts/soulbound-nft/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 00:03:47 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://lorenzozaccagnini.github.io/posts/soulbound-nft/</guid><description>Today we will develop a Soulbound NFT, an NFT that can be only minted and not traded or transferred, it is bounded to the first owner. We&amp;rsquo;ll do it using foundry with hardhat integrated. The Github workflow will test (foundry solidity and hardhat typescript) the contracts and uses Slither to statically analyze the code, trying to find the most common vulnerabilities.
You can find all the code used in my repository here</description></item></channel></rss>